[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following animals transmits the most diseases?", "correct_answer": "housefly", "incorrect_answers": ["wasp", "bee", "ant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Kevin McCallisters wise cracking brother in the movie Home Alone?", "correct_answer": "Buzz", "incorrect_answers": ["Marty", "Spike", "Bizz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nutria is native to which continent?", "correct_answer": "South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe", "Africa", "North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Not all trilobites had eyes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Islamic history, 570 A.D. was The Year of the Elephant. Which of these happened in that year?", "correct_answer": "Muhammad was born", "incorrect_answers": ["The Qur\u2019an was written in book form", "Muhammad received his first revelation", "Muhammad became ill and died"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Clydesdale is a very active horse.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous actor and director began his career on the western series Rawhide?", "correct_answer": "Clint Eastwood", "incorrect_answers": ["Rory Calhoun", "Earl Holliman", "John Wayne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1985 George A. Romero film was remade by Steve Miner in 2008.", "correct_answer": "Day of the Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["Dawn of the Dead", "Night of the Living Dead", "Zombie Holocaust"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these organs is responsible for the degradation of red blood cells?", "correct_answer": "Spleen", "incorrect_answers": ["Kidneys", "Liver", "Lungs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Under  which US President were the Barbary Wars fought?", "correct_answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "incorrect_answers": ["James K. Polk", "William McKinley", "Teddy Roosevelt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor uttered the popular phrase Keep your friends close, but your enemies closer in the 1974 movie The Godfather Part II?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Robert Duvall", "Robert De Niro", "Marlon Brando"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1997 movie Kundun directed by Martin Scorsese was based on the life of Dalai Lama. What does the Tibetan word Kundun mean?", "correct_answer": "Presence", "incorrect_answers": ["Solitude", "Eternity", "Holy"]}]